I think you hear families coming from all over Europe.
- Yes.
It's exciting!
- But in their group it is only Swedes.
- Okay.
I have no control.
I have, because I listened to them yesterday.
Should we go a little, right?
Yes.
I have to put on boots and helmets, then we drive out on the slopes.
♪ (music) ♪
- Own time.
Luxurious!
- Very good home time.
It's a thing to get in, but then you have to get out.
Yay!
A little scary when you are so high up.
We are in the gondola, on our way up to the top cabin and will have lunch.
The family is reunited!
Yes.
Did you have a good time?
(Laura Tjar) Yes, you have had so good and so much fun!
She has so much new energy when she has been with us for a while.
Yes.
- How is the ski school, then?
- It's actually fun!
- Harry, what do you think?
- It's really fun!
- Good.
- Oh.
Host, host.
Good, Laura!
Laura sits with Joanna's phone, because she is completely done.
I don't know if I like it, but it is very difficult to get something in her when she is tired and hungry.
- Obviously you don't like it.
- No.
- But the need has no law.
- No its true.
Be happy that those two eat well without screen.
- Does it taste good?
- mm.
Don't forget the vegetables, children.
- There were so many in there who were glowing at us.
- How did it feel?
- Dad.
- Yes.
Dad.
Dad has flown a little drone.
- My fingers, then.
- I canceled you.
What would you say?
Or no, Laura interrupted.
When we have lived in Portugal, we have been a bit anonymous.
You can walk around and be yourself and bark at the children when they are nasty to each other or so.
But here it feels like ... it's a little harder.
- You have eyes on you.
- Yes, a little so, but ...
You have to be your best self.
Yes, but then, it is our own choice and it is great exercise to be its best self all the time, I think.
And I love our viewers.
And I love that they arrive and that they whisper and look and point ...
- Do you just love that bit?
- No, but ... yes, that's part of it.
I love everything with what we do.
So, I don't love being known.
It sounded really strange.
But, so ... I love our viewers.
I love you!
What a tok fringes!
Now I, Alma and Harry are going to ski.
- Yes.
And me and Laura are going back to the room and lie down and rest.
How nice to you.
- Yes, I think she is freezing now.